Squid!
Oh, my God, I've never seen that before.
Shrimp!
You can't miss the conger eel!
Wow!
No way!
Hello!
I'm Miku Kanamura from Hyugaizaka 46.
Today, I'm here at the station of the world!
Yay!
Today, Miku Kanemura, aka Sushi, is going to visit a sushi restaurant in Saitama Prefecture!
Yay! Please give me your best regards!
I'm taking a selfie alone at a station in the world, and it's pretty embarrassing.
There is no sea in Saitama Prefecture.
But the sushi is really good.
I grew up here eating sushi every day.
I want to make sushi in Saitama more popular.
I'd like to do my best to make sushi in Saitama more popular.
It's so nice!
Saitama at noon is the best!
Please come to Saitama!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, you can still see the station.
Here we are!
Ta-da!
It's Senpachi Sushi!
Here we are!
This is the Seno station. Senpachi Sushi!
It really took less than 30 seconds from the station.
This time, I would like to visit this sushi restaurant.
Sushi Restaurant
Excuse me.
Hello.
We've been expecting you.
Thank you very much.
Which seat is available?
Come and get this one right here in the middle.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, I'm having lunch.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, sir, lunch.
Wow.
In a case like this.
It's full of today's eta-tails.
Lunch time.
Are you free? Are you free? I'm just curious about our family's sushi.
Well, I like a little egg, so let's try one at a time.
Yes, please.
They're in the supermarket, but if you go for two or three weeks.
I can have them brought to you.
These are the eggs
These are the eggs that are generally served everywhere.
These are for customers who really like eggs.
It's a little bit thicker.
It's really inside.
It's pretty easy to eat.
Wow.
Yeah, it's delicious.
Mmm. - Mmm.
Oh, wow.
It makes me smile.
Oh, yes.
Oh, thank you.
Yes, maido!
Okay... um... next to Mr. Goat.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Excuse me.
I don't know what to do.
Sushi, then?
What's today's special?
Blue snapper and squid.
Yarikai.
It's white.
I bought this.
I want to eat it.
And a fish called black sea bream,
And a lingcod.
Ainaame.
They have lingcod from Iwate.
Sounds delicious.
This one too,
I'm fine with lingcod, too,
For the ladies,
I'll buy some for you.
It's consistent,
Would you like to finish?
Yes, please.
Please do.
Shall I prepare the bowls?
Yes, please. Please.
Please. Shall I prepare the bowls, too? Yes, please!Please do. I'll get you a bowl, too, please! Please, please, please!
Before dipping, here are the bowls!
Oh, it's delicious!
With this Yarikai.
It's lunch, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
I'd like to have it.
Yarikai.
That's great.
Nice lunch.
Yes, it is.
Yes! Yes! Yes! That's the best lunch I've ever had.
The white meat here is Iwate lingcod.
And this is the black sea bream from Oita.
Black sea bream, yes.
Thank you very much.
A little less purple would be good.
Okay, a little less.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
We'll start with the lingcod, sea bream and squid.
Bon appétit.
May I take a few pictures?
I'll do what I do best.
I'll use my camera.
I'll take a picture of the food.
Right this way.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm.
It's sweet and elastic.
Very delicious!
I love squid.
Oh, my gosh!
This way.
Bon appétit!
It's aiame.
It's a pre-prep, isn't it, yours, that game made me think it's good in front of me, ah, yes, thanks to your treat, I think it's quite a treat.
Here you go, please take it in your mouth
Oh, thank you very much.
Here you go.
The meat is too plump.
Thai look-alike and
Freshly stocked.
I'll tell you about it.
Baba doing what Baba is holding Baba doing what Baba is holding I like what Baba is holding Baba is holding you
Baba's stocking up on barakeboo.
You look just like him, like this.
Well, thank you very much.
For coming at this time.
Thank you very much for coming at this time.
But I still like the medium fatty tuna the best.
I want some.
Chutoro?
Yes, please.
Would you like the medium fatty tuna?
I'll have the medium fatty tuna.
Chutoro would be fine, too.
But you should have the red meat before the chutoro, then the chutoro.
Yes, you're right, the oil should come later.
This red meat is very tasty.
...... delicious delicious
Yummy yummy yummy yummy
Yes. - Yes.
Yup.
That's good.
I want to take the tension.
Delicious.
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Oh, my God.
It's so crazy.
It tastes like tuna.
I love it.
Wait a minute.
It's a little hard to report!
Tasty red meat.
Tasty, isn't it?
I can eat as many as I want.
Yes, really.
Chutoro (medium fatty tuna) with a little bit of sashimi.
I'll have the chutoro.
It's super good, it's super cute, it's delicious, it's delicious.
Super tasty!
I've been telling you for a while now that it's a natural adulterant.As I said before, I'm a natural addle.
Do you like shrimp?
I love shrimp.
Live market prawns from abroad are delicious.
I'd like to eat them.
Shikamichi Island Shrimp
I highly recommend it!
Looks delicious!
I can eat the roe too.
Would you like to try some?
Eggs?
I'd like to try some.
Shrimp.
Eggs are included.
It's my first time.
Bon appétit, bon appétit!
The grains are big, so the texture is a little bit...
Delicious!
Yum!
It doesn't warm up my stomach at all.
It doesn't warm up my belly at all.
Well, I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
Conger eel.
I'd like to cut it in half.
I'll cut it in half.
The third and back nigiri.
And the back nigiri.
Two flavors.
Thank you very much.
After all, conger eel
You can't miss it!
Delicious, isn't it?
So fluffy.
Amazing!
Thank you for the food.
Wow.
Here you go.
Wow!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
Yes, sir.
Two kinds.
Two kinds of conger eel.
Looks delicious!
Beautifully presented!
Bon appétit!
If you are going to eat it, don't hold it too tight!
So many conger eels!
The wild roe is...
Wow, they are soft!
It's so warm!
I've never had warm sushi before.
Wow!
Wow.
It's gone
Mmm-hmm
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
Yum.
Delicious.
They're both really
They're so fluffy.
It gets cold, really cold.
It's so thick and fluffy.
Delicious.
You know what? Where are we going today?
Eh?
I got a piece of squid from the sea called squid's mantis.
Yes, sir.
How do you like it?
Yes, and then...
And the natural tuna with scallion and leeks.
Yes, thank you.
That's great.
Here's the Hirado tuna with scallions.
Excuse me, what do you usually do for a living?
I'm usually an idol,
I'm usually an idol, and I'm in a group called Nakasaka46,
Do you know them?
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
They are young, but they have a good way with words.
She's easy to listen to.
I'm so nervous right now.
I'm glad.
What was the best food in the restaurant?
What was the best?
Oh, I don't know.But the conger eel was delicious.
But the conger eel was delicious, wasn't it?
The red meat was also very tasty!
I could taste the flavor more clearly than the medium fatty tuna!
He gave me the last piece.
Is that okay?
Just the first one.
I'd be happy.
Here's today's summary.
Today's summary.
Red meat is amazing!
You get this thick red meat at the end!
This is a jewel, almost
Jewelry.
Thanks for waiting all the time
I'm glad you're pleased.
Mmm.
Amazing.
Delicious.
Thank you very much. It's my pleasure.
Okay, General. Emotions, then.
Thank you very much.
Well, that was delicious.
You just said emotion.
There's one who says normal people are harmonious.
Yes, yes, yes. You just said customers are emotional. There are those who say that normal people are soppy,
But the basic concept of a customer is emotion and calculation.
But the customer is based on feelings and calculations.
That's wonderful.
Yay!
Coincidence.
I actually did some research.
I'll hold onto that for you.
That's nice. Nice smile.
Yes, I'll call you shiyo and come back.
Please do.
So.
I'm done eating.
No, it was a wonderful restaurant.
The food was delicious and the ingredients were fresh,
It was my ideal sushi restaurant.
I felt it was very important to have this kind of opportunity for conversation.
I was even allowed to take pictures,
I'm so glad I was able to be a part of this event.
Please subscribe to the Hinataka channel and give us a high rating and a good button.
♪♪♪